

#### PERSONAL DETAILS

Surname Roberts
First Names Jihaad

**ID Number** 000111 5227 082

**Gender** Male

Nationality South African

Address 21 Portland Road, Salt River 7925

**Contact Number** 064 503 0924

Email Address jihaadroberts@gmail.com
Social Media jihaadroberts@gmail.com
Instagram.com/mr\_roberts22

Driver's License No

**Languages** English, Afrikaans, Arabic(Basic)

### **PROFILE**

Frontend web developer and designer with 2+ years experience using WordPress or from scratch using HTML, CSS and Javascript and the frameworks that go with it such as Bootstrap, jquery etc. I am also able to code in C# and basic Python and is able to use the Unity game engine for game development.

Apart from that I also do 3D modelling using the Blender software and advanced photo editing and video editing using Adobe Photoshop and Filmora9 software respectively.

## **EDUCATION**

 Al Azhar High School, Cape Town (Jan 2016 – Nov 2019)

#### **Matriculated Subjects:**

- English
- Afrikaans
- Mathematics
- Physical Science
- Biology
- Arabic
- Life Orientation
- Madina Institute, Cape Town (Jan 2020 – May 2020)

# **OTHER**

- Learn C#, Code Academy Pro... [Completed]
   (Nov 2017 Jan 2018)
- Learn HTML, Code Academy Pro... [Completed]
   (Jan 2018 Mar 2018)
- Learn CSS, Code Academy Pro... [Completed]
   (Mar 2018 Jun 2018)
- Learn JavaScript, Code Academy Pro... [Completed] (Jun 2018 – Sep 2018)
- Learn ASP.NET, Razor Pages, Code Academy Pro... [Still Busy]
   (August 2021 Not Completed)

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

- Mechanic Assistant at Jumbo Parts, Cape Town (Jan 2018 – Mar 2018)
  - Job mostly included the stripping of car parts, carrying of tools and the occasional stock take.
- Installer's Assistant at Revelation Audio, Cape Town (Jan 2019 – June 2019)
  - Job included the carrying of heavy tools, drilling, grinding, gluing and stock take.
- Waiter at Classique Cafe (weekends only), Cape Town (Jan 2021 – April 2021)
  - Job included the carrying of heavy tools, drilling, grinding, gluing and stock take.
- Programmer and Photo Editor at Kaotec, Cape Town (July 2020 – August 2021)
  - Job included debugging of pre-existing code, improving existing programs and Retouching real estate images using Adobe Photoshop.

#### TECHNICAL/SPECIAL SKILLS

- Able to code in C#,HTML,CSS and Javascript
- Basic 3D modelling using Blender software
- Can solve a Rubiks Cube in under 30 seconds
- Sketching
- WordPress Web Development
- Adobe Photoshop
- Unity

# **OTHER SKILLS**

- · Active listening
- Hardworking with unyielding tenacity to succeed at anything I put my mind to.
- Presentation and public speaking.
- · Creativity and problem solving
- Teamwork

## **PERSONAL PROJECTS**

- Developed an android game called "Sky High" currently available on Playstore.
- Developed a blog website call grabamindful.com
- Developed 2 business websites, namely thedesignspider.com and barnesgrxphstudios.com
- Developed and designed a bunch of concept websites from scratch using only HTML,CSS and JavaScript (Everything available on portfolio)

## **HOBBIES / INTERESTS**

Chess, soccer, sprinting, coding/computer programming, solving puzzles, reading, writing poetry and artificial intelligence.

# PERSONAL GOAL AND OBJECTIVES

My personal goal is to start multiple companies/streams of income in order to achieve financial freedom and support my family and those in need by utilizing my full potential and skills. My personal objectives are to deliver the best performance, regardless of the challenge given to me, to always maintain good working skills and relationships with colleagues and clients/customers, to never give up and always create room for self-development.

I, Jihaad, declare that the particulars furnished above are true and correct. I enclose my CV for your consideration. I would like to tell you more about my suitability for the role at an interview and would be pleased to meet with you. Thank you for your time assessing through my curriculum vitae.

0645030924, jihaadroberts@gmail.com